Inventory of the Broadside Case Collection, 1896 - 2004
Broadside Case Collection, 1896 - 2004
- Buildings: Olin Library and McKim, Mead & White Campus
  - Olin Library, 1980
    - Sketch of the West elevation of the proposed Dietrich reading room. Duplicate
    - Sketch of the North elevation of the proposed Dietrich reading room. Duplicate
    - Sketch of the South elevation of the proposed Dietrich reading room. Duplicate
    - Sketch of Floor plan of Proposed Dietrich Reading Room. Duplicate.
    - Sketch of Jakobson Periodical Reading Room. Duplicate Carbon Copy.
    - Additions to Buildings by New England Architects, 1971-82, exhibition poster, 1983, featuring Olin Library addition.
    - Colin and Nancy Campbell Reference Center dedication notice, poster, ca. 1984.
  - Olin Memorial Library. Original Plans (McKim, Mead, & White). Blueprints.
    - Olin Library, labeled 4-7
    - Olin Library, labeled 1-1
    - Olin Library, labeled 1-2
    - Olin Library, labeled 1-3
    - Olin Library, labeled 1-4
    - Olin Library, labeled 1-5
    - Olin Library, labeled 1-7
    - Olin Library, labeled 1-9
    - Olin Library, labeled 1-10
    - Olin Library, labeled 1-11
    - Olin Library, labeled 1-12
    - Olin Library, labeled 1-13
    - Olin Library, labeled 1-14
    - Olin Library, unlabeled
    - Olin Library, unlabeled
    - Bound stack of blueprints of Olin Library
  - Campus plan blueprint, 1913
  - Olin Memorial Library. Original Plans (McKim, Mead, and White). Drawings
    - Memorial Hall.
    - Detail of Portico etc.
    - Plan of Portico and Steps.
    - Exterior Window. Details etc.
    - Miscellaneous Exterior Details.
    - Detail of Stone Joints in Base Course.
    - Cornerstone.
    - Detail of Upper Stories of Stack Room. Rear Elevation.
    - Shop Drawing revision. Marble and Granite.
    - Sections Thro' Main Cornice and Roof.
    - Detail of Fresh Air Intake. Main Elevation.
    - Detail Showing Typical Treatment of Elevator Shaft.
    - Detail of North Wall of Machine Room Showing Duct Opening.
    - Tracing. Rough Frames for Interior Basement Doors in Conc. Walls.
    - Tracing. Main Stair.
    - Incised Inscription in Frieze Over Main Portico.
    - Detail Plan of Men's Toilet Room in the Basement.
    - Detail Plan of Women's Toilet Room in the Basement.
    - Detail Plan of Librarian's Toilet Room - First Floor.
    - Detail Plan of Men's Toilet Room - Third Floor.
    - Method of Draining Stack Room Floors - North Wall.
    - Main Reading Room.
    - Memorial Hall.
    - Memorial Hall Floor and Ceiling.
    - Browsing Room - Second Floor.
    - Spacing of Bookcase Division - Main Reading Room.
    - Lower Reading Room Details.
    - Pedestals for Busts at Ends of Memorial Hall.
    - Revised Dimensions Around Marble Pilasters in Delivery Space.
    - Diagram Showing Location of Rosettes in Ornamented Plaster Borders at Ends of Mem. Hall.
    - Center Ornament - Mosaic Fl. Memorial Hall.
    - Inscriptions on End Walls of Memorial Hall.
    - Rubber Floor in Delivery Space.
    - Door Schedule. Excepting - Outside, Elevator, and LeathrCov. Doors.
    - Part Elevation of Delivery Space Showing Electric Outlets.
    - Memorial Hall. Steel Frames for Arched Opening Between Mem. Hall and 2nd Floor Corridor.
    - Typical Lavatory and Location of Mirror, Glass Shelf and Soap Dish.
    - Pilaster at Side of Arched Opening 2nd Fl. Corridor Looking Toward Memorial Hall.
    - Grille in East Wall of Lower Reading Room.
    - Revised Details in Spec. Coll. Rms 3rd Fl.
    - Marble Spandrils 2nd Floor Arched Windows East End of Building.
    - Marble Panel at Head of Window at Memorial Hall (Main Portico).
    - Wood Doors, Jambs, and Trim.
    - Register on South Wall of Stack Room.
    - Typical Doors to W. C. Compartments.
    - Spandrel Mould of Window Arch Browsing Rm. (Revised).
    - Typical Wall Rail & Bracket.
    - Door From Corridor to Stack Rm. - N. Side of Elevator.
    - Leather Covered Doors for Door Between Delivery Space and Stack Room - 1st Fl.
    - Olin Memorial Library. Elevation of Interior of Entrance.
    - Delivery Desk and Filing Cases.
    - Plan of 3rd floor and Roof.
    - Design for Benches in Davison Art Rooms.
    - Arrangement of Tables in Reading Room.
    - Part of East and West Elevation.
  - Olin Memorial Library, Subsequent renovation plans, 1931-1965. Drawings.
    - Scheme A, October 24, 1935
    - Exterior Details, March 14, 1938
    - Section Thro C of Bldg. Looking West, October 10, 1933
    - Reading Room Clock Dial, Aug. 25, 1931.
    - Plan of First and Second Floors, March 14, 1938.
    - North Elevation and Section Looking South, March 14, 1938.
    - East Elevation and Section Looking West, March 14, 1938.
    - Details of Wall Chases, June 2, 1938.
    - (Doors.) Third Floor, July 5, 1938.
    - Changes in Duct Work etc, Aug. 30, 1938.
    - The Third Floor Plan, June 16, 1965.
  - Olin Memorial Library, Subsequent Renovation Plans, 1929-1959. Blueprints.
    - Double-faced Exhibition Case, October 28, 1929.
    - Layout Plan of Attic Floor, January 31, 1935.
    - Layout Plan of Attic Floor, white copy paper.
    - Carbon Copy of Blueprint. 4-1
    - Carbon Copy of Blueprint. 4-2
    - Carbon Copy of Blueprint. 4-3
    - Carbon Copy of Blueprint. 4-4
    - Carbon Copy of Blueprint. 4-5
    - Proposed New Posts Etc. At East & West Ends of Balustrade North of Olin Library. April 23, 1938.
    - Olin Memorial Library Terrace. July 27, 1938.
    - Alterations to Olin Library for Rare Book Room. Basement Plan. April 1952.
    - Alterations to Olin Library for Rare Book Room. Floor and Ceiling Plans. Rare Book Room and Study Room. Elevations of Study Room. April 1952
    - Alterations to Olin Library for Rare Book Room. North and South Elevations of Rare Book Room. April 1952
    - Alterations to Olin Library for Rare Book Room. Elevation and Detail of East Wall of Rare Book Room. April 1952
    - Alterations to Olin Library for Rare Book Room. Elevation and Detail of West Wall and Fireplace of Rare Book Room. April 1952
    - Alterations to Olin Library for Rare Book Room. Details of Cornice and Typical Book Case. Rare Book Room. April 1952
    - Alterations to Olin Library for Rare Book Room. Comparative Shelving Plans - 3rd floor. Half Plan Scheme 'B.' July 1952. Duplicate.
    - Alterations to Olin Library for Rare Book Room. Comparative Shelving Plans - 3rd floor. Half Plan Scheme 'D.' July 1952. Duplicate.
    - Bound packet of blueprints, blue ink on white paper. Heating, Ventilating, and Air Conditioning. Set of 7 sheets.
      - HVAC 1
      - HVAC 2
      - HVAC 3
      - HVAC 4
      - HVAC 5
      - HVAC 6
      - HVAC 7
    - Bound packet of blueprints. Alterations. Set of 3 sheets. February 1959
      - A1. Section Thru Elevator Shaft - Detail, Plans of Shaft & Pit.
      - A2. Basement. First and Second Floor Plans.
      - A3. Plan of 3rd Floor.
    - Bound packet of blueprints. Alterations. Set of 4 sheets. February 1959
      - A1. Section Thru Elevator Shaft - Detail, Plans of Shaft & Pit. Duplicate of previous entry.
      - A3. Plan of 3rd Floor. Duplicate of previous entry.
      - A2. Basement. First and Second Floor Plans. Duplicate of previous entry.
      - A4. Attic Plan - Steel Framing.
    - Blueprint. Additional Telephone Conduit. Drawing 49. September 1954
  - Olin Memorial Library. Original and Subsequent Plans, 1926-1962.
    - Bound Packet of Prints/Carbon Copies, purple ink on white paper. Set of 7 Sheets. February 1926.
      - 2-1. Heating and Ventilating. Basement Plan at Floor.
      - 2-2. Heating and Ventilating. Basement Plan at Ceiling.
      - 2-3. Heating and Ventilating. First Floor Plan.
      - 2-4. Heating and Ventilating. Second Floor Plan.
      - 2-5. Heating and Ventilating. Third Floor Plan.
      - 2-6. Heating and Ventilating. Attic Plan.
      - 2-7. Heating and Ventilating. Riser Diagram.
    - Print. Third Floor Part Plan. August 1974
    - Print. Basement Floor Plan. No Date.
    - Prints (3). Basement Floor Plan. No Date. Duplicate, with additions in pink ink.
    - Print. First Floor Plan. No Date. Additions in pink ink.
    - Print. Second Floor Plan. No Date.
    - Bound Packet of Prints, black ink on white paper. Set of 7 sheets, one of them detached. December 7, 1937.
      - Addition to Olin Memorial Library. Basement Plan.
      - Addition to Olin Memorial Library. First Floor Plan.
      - Addition to Olin Memorial Library. Second Floor Plan.
      - Addition to Olin Memorial Library. North Elevation.
      - Addition to Olin Memorial Library. East Elevation.
      - Addition to Olin Memorial Library. Rear Elevation.
      - Addition to Olin Memorial Library. North Elevation. This sheet is disconnected from the packet, and is a duplicate of the other North Elevation print. It is very faded.
    - Print. Corridor Plan. Layout of Rooms 36, 37, 38 Olin Library for Wesleyan Archives Collection. No Date. Duplicate.
    - Print. Alterations for New Circulation Desk. Olin Library - First Floor Corridor. February 2, 1962.
    - Print. Folding Gate Details. October 5, 1953.
    - Print. Furnishing Plan for Work Room. July 2, 1952.
    - Print. Furnishing Plan for Work Room. July 2, 1952. Duplicate, with additions in pencil.
    - Print. Ceiling Plan. Sketch For a Room for a Collection of Rare Books for George W. Davison Esq. November 7, 1951. Duplicate
    - Print. Rare Book Room Furnishing Plan. June 3, 1952.
  - Olin Memorial Library. Original Plans and Subsequent Renovations, 1926-1938 (McKim, Mead, and White)
    - Print, gray waxy paper. Front Elevation. February 11, 1926.
    - Print, gray waxy paper. East Elevation. February 11, 1926.
    - Print, gray waxy paper. Second Floor Plan. February 11, 1926.
    - Print, gray waxy paper. West Elevation. February 11, 1926.
    - Print, gray waxy paper. Longitudinal Section. February 11, 1926.
    - Print, gray waxy paper. Attic Floor Plan. February 11, 1926.
    - Print, gray waxy paper. Transverse Section. February 11, 1926.
    - Print, gray waxy paper. Rear Elevation. February 11, 1926.
    - Print, gray waxy paper. Plot Plan. February 11, 1926.
    - Print, gray waxy paper. Foundation Plan. February 11, 1926.
    - Print, gray waxy paper. Basement Floor Plan. February 11, 1926.
    - Print, gray waxy paper. Details. February 11, 1926.
    - Print, gray waxy paper. Heating and Ventilation, Riser Diagram. February 11, 1926.
    - Print, gray waxy paper. Heating and Ventilation, First and Second Floor Plan. February 11, 1926.
    - Print, gray waxy paper. Heating and Ventilation, Third Floor Plan. February 11, 1926.
- Buildings - Plans
  - Pine Street Dance Studio, 2002, I (Drawer 13)
    - Packet. Plans for "New Dance Studio, 247 Pine Street." Set of 34 Sheets. Black printer ink on white paper.
      - Title Page.
      - Site-Demolition Plan.
      - Layout and Landscaping Plan.
      - Site Grading and Utility Plan.
      - Existing Condition Map.
      - Site Details and Planning Guidelines.
      - General notes, Building Codes, Toilet Room Mounting Heights.
      - Door Schedule; Window Schedule, Wall Types and Misc. Details.
      - Crawl Space Floor Plan.
      - Floor Plan.
      - Roof Plan.
      - Exterior Elevations.
      - Building Sections.
      - Reflected Ceiling Plan.
      - Wall Sections and Details.
      - Design Basis & Notes.
      - Crawl Space and Foundation Plan and Details.
      - First Floor Framing Plan and Details.
      - Roof and Mechanical Attic Framing Plans.
      - Typical Details.
      - Truss Elevations and Details.
      - Crawl Space Fire Protection.
      - First Floor Fire Protection.
      - Attic Fire Protection.
      - Fire Protection Details.
      - First Floor Plumbing Plan.
      - Crawl Space Plumbing Plan.
      - First Floor HVAC Plan.
      - Lighting Plan.
      - Power Plan.
      - Light and Power - Crawl Space.
      - Fire Alarm.
      - Electrical Details and Specs.
  - Pine Street Dance Studio, 2002, II
    - Mounted samples of carpet, vinyl, and tile.
  - Clark Hall, mounted floor plans
    - First Floor.
    - Ground Floor.
    - Second Floor.
    - Third Floor.
    - Fourth Floor.
  - Olin Library Floor Plans
    - Print. Negative copy. Third Floor Plan.
    - Print. Second Floor Plan.
    - Print. First Floor Plan.
    - Print. Basement Floor Plan.
    - Print. Second Floor Plan. (5)
    - Blueprint. First Floor Plan. January 1923
    - Blueprint. Library Bureau
    - Print. Science Center. Phase II. First Floor Plan. Library Wing. February 1970
    - Print. Science Center. Phase II. Second Floor Plan. Library Wing. February 1970
    - Blueprint. Plan of Reception Room. Office of Henry Bacon Archt.
    - Print. Olin Library Addition. North Elevation and Section Looking South. March 1938.
    - Blueprint. Layout Plan of Attic Floor Showing Layout of Metal Bookcases.
    - Print on white, waxy paper. Third Floor Plan.
  - Center for the Arts - Roche and Dinkeloo
    - Print A1. Site Plan.
    - Print A2. Building No. 1.
    - Print A3. Building No. 2.
    - Print A4. Building No. 3, Building No. 4. Floor Plans.
    - Print A5. Building No. 3, Building No. 4. Elevations.
    - Print A6. Building No. 3, Building No. 4. Sections
    - Print A7. Building No. 5.
    - Print A8. Building No. 6.
    - Print A9. Building No. 7.
    - Print A10. Building No. 7, Building No. 8, Building No. 9.
    - Print A11. Building No. 10.
    - Print A12. Building No. 11 Floor Plans.
    - Print A13. Building No. 11.
    - Print A14. Building No. 12 Floor Plans.
    - Print A15. Building No. 12.
    - Print A15. Building No. 13.
    - Print A17. Building No. 13 Elevations.
    - Print A18. Building No. 13 Sections.
    - Print A19. Building No. 14.
  - Center for the Arts
    - Print. Site Plan. 1968-69.
    - Print. Building K. Library. 1968-69.
  - Proposed Music Building and Auditorium, May/July 1955. Charles H. Warner, Jr. Architect. 4 Schemes.
    - Packet of 11 Prints on tan/yellow paper.
      - Scheme 1. Site Plan.
      - Scheme 1. Lower Level Plan.
      - Scheme 1. Upper Level Plan.
      - Scheme 2. Site Plan.
      - Scheme 2. Lower Level Plan.
      - Scheme 2. Upper Level Plan.
      - Scheme 3. Site Plan.
      - Scheme 3. Main Level Plan.
      - Scheme 4. Upper Level Plan.
      - Scheme 4. Lower Level Plan.
      - Scheme 4. Appears to be the Site Plan.
  - Science Center - Blueprints [Acc. 2001-37]
    - Science Library Renovation. Study #2. October 1982.
    - Science Library Renovation. Study #1. October 1982.
    - Science Center. Second Floor Reflected Ceiling Plan, Library Wing.
    - Wesleyan Science Library. 2 Tier Stacks.
    - Science Center Phase II. Second Floor Plan, Library Wing.
    - Science Library Renovations. Second Floor. October 1982.
    - Science Library Renovations. Second Floor. Plan Utilizing Existing Furnishings. October 1982.
    - Science Library Renovations. Basement. October 1982.
    - Science Center Phase II. (2 copies)
    - Wesleyan Science Tower.
    - Science Center Phase II. First Floor Plan. Library Wing.
    - Science Center Phase II. Ground Floor Plan.
  - Judd Hall I
    - Pen and ink drawing, waxed paper. Front Elevation, Dec. 1869.
    - Pen and ink drawing, waxed paper. North Elevation, Dec. 1869.
    - Pen and ink drawing, waxed paper. Plan of Second Story, Dec. 1869.
    - Pen and ink drawing, waxed paper. Plan of Third Story, Dec. 1869.
    - Print, illustration of Judd Hall with text and floor plans, 4 copies, ca. 1870
  - Judd Hall II
    - Blueprint. East Elevation, Preliminary Sketch. January 1957
    - Blueprint. North Elevation, Preliminary Sketch. January 1957
    - Blueprint. East Elevation, Preliminary Sketch B. November 1951
    - Blueprints. Packet of 6 sheets. November 1956.
      - Preliminary Sketch B for Allocation of Space.
      - First Floor Plan (Psychology).
      - Second Floor Plan (Psychology).
      - Third Floor Plan (Geology).
      - Forth Floor Plan (Geology).
      - Pent House Plan (Geology).
    - Blueprint. Preliminary Sketch for Allocation of Space. Basement Plan (Psychology). January 1957.
    - Blueprint. Preliminary Sketch for Allocation of Space. First Floor Plan (Psychology). January 1957.
    - Blueprint. Preliminary Sketch for Allocation of Space. Second Floor Plan (Psychology). January 1957.
    - Blueprint. Preliminary Sketch for Allocation of Space. Third Floor Plan (Geology). January 1957.
    - Blueprint. Preliminary Sketch for Allocation of Space. Fourth Floor Plan (Geology). January 1957.
    - Blueprint. Preliminary Sketch for Allocation of Space. Attic Plan (Psychology). January 1957.
    - Drawing, pencil. Waxy Yellow paper attached to tan paper. Natural History Cabinets.
    - Drawing, Pencil. Alterations to Judd Hall.
    - Folder. 22 Blueprints 1958. Set of 22 8.5 x 11 inch blueprints.
    - Sheet 1. Laboratory Rooms. Rooms D3, D4, D5, D7. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 2. Laboratory Room. Rooms D6, D8. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 3. Laboratory Rooms. Rooms D9, D10, D11, D12. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 4. Storage Room. Rooms D13. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 5. Observation Room. Rooms D16. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 6. Class Room. Rooms D17. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 7. Class Room. Classroom and Closet. Room D105, D104. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 8. Psychology Department Library. Room D111. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 9. Office No. 2. Room D116. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 10. Office No. 1. Room D117. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 11. Records and Record Booth. Rooms D118, D119. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 12. Office No. 3. Room D201. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 13. Office No. 4. Room D202. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 14. Office No. 5. Room D205. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 15. Office No. 6. Room D206. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 16. Psychology Secretary's Office. Room D207. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 17. Psychology Chairman's Office No. 7. Room D208. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 18. Office No. 8. Room D209. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 20. Distinction Work Room. Room D218. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 21. Office No. 1. Room D219. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 22. Office No. 2. Room D220. Room Furnishings.
    - Sheet 40. Animal Rooms 1,2,3,4,5, and Incinerator Room. Rooms D505, D506, D512, D513, D515, D517. Room Furnishings.
  - Carbon Copy of Illustration of Judd Hall.
  - Bound packet of carbon copies. Set of 7 Sheets.
    - East elevation, Preliminary Sketch B.
    - Basement Plan (Psychology). Preliminary Sketch C for Allocation of Space.
    - First Floor Plan (Psychology). Preliminary Sketch C for Allocation of Space.
    - Second Floor Plan (Psychology). Preliminary Sketch C for Allocation of Space.
    - Third Floor Plan (Geology). Preliminary Sketch C for Allocation of Space.
    - Fourth Floor Plan (Geology). Preliminary Sketch C for Allocation of Space.
    - Pent House Plan (Geology). Preliminary Sketch C for Allocation of Space.
  - Hall Lab Plans, McKim, Mead, and White, September 9, 1925
    - Drawing No. 2: Basement Floor Plan.
    - Drawing No. 3: First Floor Plan.
    - Drawing No. 4: Second Floor Plan.
    - Drawing No. 5: Third Floor and Roof Plan.
    - Drawing No. 6: Elevations.
    - Drawing No. 7: Sections.
  - Unidentified Campus Plans, ca. 1900? Brownstone Row (large print on white waxy paper)
  - Science Library
    - Print. Ground Floor Plan. 6/67.
    - Print. First Floor Plan.
    - Print. Second Floor Plan.
    - Print. Science Center: Phase II. Site Plan. 6/67.
    - Print. Science Center: Phase II. Basement Plan Library Wing. 12/67.
    - Print. Science Center: Phase II. Ground Plan Library Wing. 8/67.
    - Print. Science Center: Phase II. First Floor Plan Library Wing. 8/67.
    - Print. Science Center: Phase II. Second Floor Plan Library Wing. 8/67.
    - Print. Science Center: Phase II. Core Plan and sections. 8/67.
  - Science Building [Scott Lab]
    - Blueprint. Basement Plan.
    - Blueprint. First Story Plan.
    - Blueprint. Second Story Plan.
    - Blueprint. Third Story Plan.
  - Scott Laboratory Plans. Rooms 2-7, SE Corner.
    - Print on white waxy paper. SE Corner, Scott Labs, from Orig. Plans.
    - Print on white waxy paper. Rooms 2-7, Scott Labs, Traced from Original Plan. 1/31.
  - Panoramic picture of plans of new building next to Olin Library, where the Campus center currently stands.
  - Proposed Library - Design Development Plans, Franzen, circa early 1970s.
    - Print A1. Wesleyan University Library Schematic Design Phase. Basement. 9/72
    - Print A2. Wesleyan University Library Schematic Design Phase. Level 1. 9/72
    - Print A3. Wesleyan University Library Schematic Design Phase. Main Entry Level. 9/72
    - Print A4. Wesleyan University Library Schematic Design Phase. Level 2. 9/72
    - Print A6. Wesleyan University Library Schematic Design Phase. Penthouse. 9/72
    - Print. Wesleyan University Library Schematic Design Phase. Location Plan. 9/72
    - Print. Exterior Wall Materials Study. 9/72
    - Wesleyan University Library. Design Development Phase. 7/73
      - Print G1. Site Plan.
      - Print G2. Plaza Plan.
      - Print G3. Site Demolition, Grading, Paving, and Planting.
      - Print G4. Site Utilities Plan.
      - Print A1. Basement.
      - Print A2. Level 1.
      - Print A3. Main Entry Level.
      - Print A4. Level 2.
      - Print A5. Level 3.
      - Print A6. Penthouse and Roof.
      - Print A7. Elevations.
      - Print A8. Elevations.
      - Print A9. Sections.
      - Print A10. Wall Sections 1 Thru 4.
      - Print A11. Wall Sections 5 Thru 8.
      - Print A12. Reflected Ceiling Plan.
      - Print A13. Main Entry Level Reflected Ceiling Plan.
      - Print A14. Level 2 Reflected Ceiling Plan.
      - Print A15. Level 3 and Penthouse Reflected Ceiling Plan.
      - Print A16. Axonometric View of Lobby.
      - Print S1. Foundation
      - Print S2. Level 1 Framing.
      - Print S3. Main Entry Level Framing.
      - Print S4. Level 2 Framing.
      - Print S5. Level 3 Framing.
      - Print S6. Penthouse and Roof Framing.
      - Print HVAC1. Basement.
      - Print HVAC2. Level 1.
      - Print HVAC3. Main Entry Level.
      - Print HVAC4. Level 2.
      - Print HVAC5. Level 3.
      - Print HVAC6. Penthouse and Roof.
      - Print P1. Basement.
      - Print P2. Level 1.
      - Print P3. Main Entry Level.
      - Print P4. Level 2.
      - Print P5. Level 3.
      - Print P6. Penthouse and Roof.
      - Print E1. Basement.
      - Print E2. Level 1.
      - Print E3. Main Entry Level.
      - Print E4. Level 2.
      - Print E5. Level 3.
      - Print E6. Penthouse and Roof.
  - Fan Foundation #2. Water Tube Boiler. Boiler Foundation and Misc. Iron and Steel. Van Zelm, Heywood, and Shadford, Cons. Engineers. 8/25/65.
    - Fan Foundation #2 Boiler. 9/65.
    - Boiler Foundation and Misc. Iron and Steel. Installation of New Boiler. 8/65. Duplicate
    - Carbon Copy, blue ink with pink additions. Layout of One 28,500 #/Hr "KS-20" Bigelow Water Tube BLR - 160# DES. Drawing Number KS-202-1A. 6/58. Duplicate.
    - Carbon Copy, blue ink with pink additions. Layout of One 36,000 3/Hr "KS-22" Bigelow Water Tube Boiler - 160 # Design. Drawing Number KS-225-IA. 7/58.
    - Carbon Copy, blue ink. Layout of One 36,000 3/Hr "KS-22" Bigelow Water Tube Boiler - 160 # Design. Drawing Number KS-225-IB. 7/58.
  - Boiler Foundation and Misc. Iron and Steel.
    - BR II. Fan Foundation #2 Boiler. 9/65.
    - BP II. Boiler Foundation & Misc. Iron and Steel Installation of New Boiler. 6/58.
    - BP I. Installation of Boiler Plan Equipment. 7/58
    - BP 3. Installation of Boiler Plan Equipment. 7/58
    - BR1. Boiler Foundation and Misc. Iron and Steel Installation of New Boiler. 8/65
    - BR2. Installation #2 Boiler. 8/65
    - BP2. Installation of Boiler Plan Equipment. 7/58